No I'm sorry that you know
that will be able to play with you
boys till later this afternoon.
He's doing some work for me right.
Hi I hope I never see another Springer's
or there's irony of oh you're the spinner.
Well OK Mr thank you so is
that wish Who were you then finally
the spice they call me
Joe when the get it.
No response from our son.
Not to.
My friends not play.
Gee Carly I didn't realize what I was wishing
I'm sorry for everything I said can't
we call the whole thing off.
Is there anything I can do.
Please let me take back my
wish. OK after just going.
But the next time they kept the.
It seems that almost the scientific
principle of a spring is to absorb energy
and then to release it.
That's all there is to learn
to read you know.
Here are nice
Yes it was
but if it wasn't for the amount of playing
in the club sample combined with the
spring of the rubber inside the ball
that drive would have gone anywhere
and all you see all spring action depends
on elasticities the ability of material
to return to its original form after
it's been forced out of shape.
You know like the action of a springboard
and when you stop to think about it.
Even the grown the notice
like a heel spring.
It has the ability to a problem blows
and then transmit the shock
from one point to another
and that's exactly what the spring is
supposed to do transmit shock from one point
to another all came up.
Let's get on with the game.
You don't realize the number of
springs that work for us every day.
Why there's a little spring
in your cigarette lighter
and the spring in your pencil
clear and the huge strings
that cushion the railroad trains.
Why I could name thousands of
everyday uses for springs.
I never realize until lately the springs
have such a universal you why there's
strangely in mousetraps
guns exercises in Congo
sticks.
Why it's practically impossible to name a
single thing in which some sort of thing
is an essential in one way or another
take that plane up there for instance.
Yes Can a set of shock
absorbers on the wheel
that depend on heavy springs
controlled by hydraulic current
when the ship lands that springs
eased the shock so much.
You can't even tell when
you're on the ground
and as far as an automobile is concerned
I wouldn't even attempt to tell you how
many various kinds of planes are
you in addition to the strain
of the problem of people like you guys is
that just because more springs are usually
hidden you some of them think of the
important part they play
in the regular operation
and enjoyment of our cars produces just
take the springs I mentioned a while ago
the strings are built under the car to
provide complete writing compass spiral coil
springs an immediate action in front
balanced a lead of the car with leaf springs
in the rear so that the body
always rides on an even keel.
Can you imagine what it would be like riding
along a rough road like this with also
special Springs
and then to the springs in the same back
cushion to take up any other little bumps
that get through to the body of the car
service cars right in comfort is concerned
the tires the cushion springs under special
springs on the car all combined to give
us a ride that can't be touched.
He just wake up wake up from
us well that didn't take long.
You played a great game boy much you lost
what you need is a little more spring in
the punning you win years brings
I hope I never see another
cop who said you will never lose anything
like that as long as you want to.